[monitor beeping]
[monitor tone]
[roosters cawing]
[mystical music]
- [Hiraku] I was dreaming?
It's been a long time
since I've dreamt that.
- Lord Hiraku.
I'm terribly sorry,
I still haven't finished
the morning chores.
- Don't worry,
I woke up early today.
Anyways, I'd appreciate it if
you stopped calling me lord.
- Right, very well, mayor.
- [Maid] Oh, good morning.
- [Hiraku] Ha, good morning.
[sighs]
[stuff crashes]
[slime bubbling]
- Sorry, I was being careless.
- So you're working in
the kitchen now?
- I'll just roast
the whole thing.
- [Hiraku] No, cut him
some slack.
[slime vocalizes]
[cheerful pastoral music]
[Hiraku exhales]
- Oh?
What a surprise.
You're up early today,
aren't you?
- I am, I wanted to get
an early start.
- [Tia] Good morning.
- What are you doing here?
- I had to talk to Granmary
about something
while she was on patrol duty.
- [Lu] Is there a problem?
- It's nothing like that.
She reported to me earlier
about something, and...
[Lu and Tia hum]
Is something wrong?
- Hm?
No, it's nothing.
I just had a dream
I haven't had in a while.
- [Lu] A dream?
- Well, actually, it's
more like an old memory.
[children giggling]
[upbeat pastoral music]
Back then, I really never
could have imagined,
that I'd ever get to live
such a dream of a life.
["Flower Ring" by
Shino Shimoji, Aya Suzaki plays]
- [God] Hiraku Machio.
That's you, isn't it?
- [Hiraku] Yes?
And, um, you are?
- [God] I'm the god who
watches over this world.
- [Hiraku] You're God?
Ah, I guess that means
I finally died.
- [God] Indeed.
According to this world's
calendar you've lived 39 years.
And what a cruel life it was.
You were betrayed by others,
and then fell ill with
a terminal disease.
That's why, I've decided
to give you a chance
at a second life.
- [Hiraku] You can do that?
- [God] Of course, I'm God.
This time I shall grant you
a healthy body
that won't fall ill.
You see, I consider it
a mistake on my part
that you were forced to live
such a cruel existence
in the first place.
- [Hiraku] Your mistake?
- [God] I ask that you
take this act
as penance for my misdeed.
- [Hiraku] Oh, I don't really
get it, but okay.
- [God] Well, let's make sure
to do this right.
Do you have any requests?
I'll let you live your new life
the way you want to.
- [Hiraku] The way I want to?
- [God] I can grant pretty much
any request you have.
- [Hiraku] In that case,
I've got it,
I want to try my hand
at farming.
- [God] Farming?
- [Hiraku] Yeah, I really
liked watching a show
about farming while I was
stuck in the hospital.
- [God] Mm-hmm.
- [Hiraku] It was a show
about celebrities farming.
In my last life,
I had a hard time
getting along with
other people,
so I thought it would be nice
if I could live a laid back
life of farming
somewhere where
not many people go.
Is that too much to ask?
- [God] No, it's just that
farming isn't part of
my jurisdiction.
- [Hiraku] Your jurisdiction?
- [God] But let's give 'em
a call and see.
Ah, hm, okay.
It is done, you'll
receive your new life
and a healthy body
with which to live it.
I've also received permission
from the god of agriculture
to bestow upon you the power of
the almighty farming tool.
- [Hiraku] The almighty
farming tool?
- [God] Now then, enjoy your
chance at a second life.
[mystical music]
[Hiraku grunting]
[leaves rustling]
- My body can move.
It's been a long time since
I've been able to move around.
How many years has it been
since I could stand?
Having a healthy body,
is amazing.
Alright, I've come back
to life safe and sound.
It's time to start
my second life,
the farming life
that I wished for.
[Hiraku giggling]
[playful music]
So this is where I start?
Forest, forest as far as
the eye can see, hmm.
I know I asked for somewhere
that not many people go,
but this almost feels
like a place
that people can't reach
even if they want to.
Oh well, no use
in complaining now.
I need to think about
what I can do from here.
I'm dressed like a villager
from a video game.
And I get the feeling that
I'm younger than I used to be.
Do I have anything
I can actually use?
That's right,
the almighty farming tool.
[mystical music]
[Hiraku chuckles]
This is it, here we go.
[Hiraku grunts]
[Hiraku chuckles]
This must be magic.
No matter how much I use
this tool, I don't get tired.
I can till the hard ground
and cut through tree roots
no problem.
The soil is nice and fluffy.
I'm sure I can grow
some great vegetables
in a field I till with this.
Wait a minute.
I need to worry about finding
water and food right now.
[quirky music]
The forest goes on and on.
I tried listening carefully
so that I could hear if
any streams were nearby,
but all I could hear was
the rustling of the leaves.
Forget finding edible plants,
I don't see any grass
growing around here.
Am I playing on the right
difficulty setting?
[gentle suspenseful music]
Now that I think about it,
there's a good chance
that there could be dangerous
animals around here.
I need to hurry and
find somewhere safe.
Whoa, that's one nice tree.
It'll make a good landmark,
I think I'll set up
my base camp here.
[quirky music]
I walked around for a while,
but there don't seem to be
any rivers or ponds nearby.
In that case, I'll dig a well.
I bet you're thinking
that it's silly
to try to find water
underground like this.
But I've heard that people
sometimes use this method
to find water pipes, maybe.
I don't get this at all.
Shovel!
This almighty farming tool
really lives up to its name.
It can turn into
all kinds of stuff.
- Excavator!
- It can't turn into
complicated machines, though.
[Hiraku grunting]
Just as I expected,
I don't get tired
no matter how much I dig.
Now I can dig forever
until I hit water.
[Hiraku panting]
Am I stuck down here?
I know, I'll dig diagonally.
[playful music]
[water trickling]
I only just started digging.
It's my lucky day.
No, this might be another
one of God's blessings.
Now that I've secured water,
it's time to find food.
That was my plan,
but oddly enough,
I don't feel hungry at all.
I wonder if this is the power of
the almighty farming tool.
It's probably dangerous
to go wandering through
the forest again.
Scythe.
Since I'm going to turn this
into my base of operations,
I'll keep working on
building it up.
It'd be nice if I found
something to eat
while I was working here.
But I don't see anything
around here. Oh well.
If I'm going to cultivate
the land here,
this tree is going to be
in the way eventually.
Hmm.
It looks like
a pretty sturdy tree,
but maybe if I turn the
almighty tool into an ax
I can cut it down.
I think the right way is
to start cutting one side,
and then go in from
the other side with the ax.
I did it.
Hm, okay then.
I'll start from this side.
Here we go!
[dramatic pastoral music]
What the?
[screams]
I cut it clean with one swing.
This almighty farming tool
is something else.
[Hiraku laughing]
Hatchet.
Since I've already cut it down,
I should process it into lumber.
I'll start by cutting off
the branches,
then cut up the trunk
and strip the bark off.
I'm cutting through
this sturdy tree
like it's a block of cheese.
So about this hook-like tool
that I'm using to
drag the tree around.
I'm not sure what it's called,
but apparently I can turn
the almighty tool
into anything I can imagine.
[cheerful music]
Now I've got myself some lumber.
Based on the farming sim games
I used to play,
this is about the time I should
start building a small hut.
But it's not going to be easy
to build the parts for
the walls and roof.
Plus, I don't have any nails or
glue to stick them together.
Building a hut from scratch
is tougher than I thought.
Hm, this pillar I stuck in
the ground for fun
is casting a shadow
almost like a sun dial.
Oh no, I was having so much fun
that I lost track of time.
The sun's about to set and
then it's going to be night.
What happens then?
It's going to be dark out.
I need some kind of light.
Flashlight, lamp.
No good, I'll need to
start a fire.
Lighter, some matches?
Crap, maybe this has to do with
that jurisdiction thing.
Turning the almighty tool
into a match is just stupid.
I need something that can
create heat without burning up.
Bingo! Magnifying glass.
[mystical music]
It worked, I can start
a fire with this.
If it was daytime.
[quirky music]
I ended up quickly carving a
hole into the tree's trunk
so I'd have
some kind of shelter.
I thought about digging
a hole in the ground,
but the thought of accidentally
burying myself alive scared me.
This chisel is another form
of the almighty farming tool.
It looks like it'll take
a lot of trial and error
before I can make
furniture or a hut.
I was worried I wouldn't be able
to see when it was dark,
but I'm surprised at
how well I can.
Maybe it's because when God
granted me a healthy body,
my vision improved as well.
[gentle music]
Or maybe, it's because of those,
the two moons casting light.
Wow, I really am in
another world, aren't I?
[leaves rustling]
I messed around a lot
trying to figure out
how to work with the lumber,
and before I knew it,
morning had come.
[gentle music]
[water trickling]
It looks like I'll be fine
in terms of having water.
Right, I almost forgot.
[fire crackling]
[Hiraku blowing]
And now I have a fire going.
Heave-ho, heave-ho,
heave-ho, heave-ho.
From there, I continued
clearing the area
so that I could
cultivate the land.
I don't get tired or hungry
while using the
almighty farming tool,
but I'm sure that
doing this kind of work
is using up some of
my body's stamina.
Even specks of dust can
pile up to make mountains.
I think it's finally time
for me to eat something.
It might be time to change gears
and go look for food
somewhere further away.
[galloping]
[dramatic music]
[snarling]
What is that thing?
[jaunty music]
Well that was a happy accident.
I had no choice but to kill it.
It had scary fangs and stuff.
All it took was
one blow to the neck
with the almighty farming tool.
I tilled the giant rabbit's head
and turned it into
a nice fluffy soil.
Then I turned the
almighty tool into a knife
and used it to
take apart the body.
At least I'll be able
to feed myself.
I'm thankful for that.
Grilled rabbit,
it tastes very natural.
Or rather, it tastes
gamey and bloody.
Still, I'm grateful that
I have something to eat.
But, what goes in
must also come out.
The next thing I built
was a toilet.
[jaunty music]
The toilet seat was
made from a log.
Below that, I dug a hole.
[Hiraku sighs]
Now I can relax and
take care of my business.
[leaves rustling]
I can't relax at all.
I couldn't sleep either so I
used my building knowledge.
It ended up being better built
than where I actually
slept, but.
[Hiraku sighs]
A toilet that's
comfortable to use
is necessary for
any sort of civilized life.
[bright music]
I took a bunch of detours
getting here,
but I've finally started
cultivating the land.
What should I grow to help
support my life here?
I'll need stuff that
preserves well.
Potatoes?
Onions?
Some tomatoes and cucumbers
would be nice.
You can eat those as is.
Cabbage and spinach,
daikon, napa, carrots.
Oh, I want to eat
some boiled corn, too.
I've realized something here.
Even if I cultivate the land,
I have no seeds
or seedlings to plant.
I guess my only option
is to look for
something in the forest.
I went to bed on a stomach
full of rabbit meat
when I woke up the next morning,
my eyes opened in surprise
when they saw this.
[Hiraku chuckling]
Can the plants
in this world grow
even if you don't
plant their seeds?
Or could this be because of
the almighty tool?
There are sprouts
popping up in every row,
and it only took one night.
But these sprouts look different
than the plants
I'm used to seeing.
Those kind of look like
scallions, but they're bent.
Well, I'm not sure
what they are,
but even so I know
what I have to do.
I need to protect these fields
from those giant rabbits
and any other beasts
that live in this forest.
[Hiraku grunting]
First, I'll build a fence
around the perimeter.
Then, I'll dig a ditch
around the fence.
[bright music]
I'm still a little worried,
but I feel a lot better
having this built.
After a few days, the fence
and the ditch were completed.
During that time, I fed myself
from another rabbit
that tried charging
into my fields.
I wonder why they always
charge in headfirst like that.
Maybe I'm what they're
trying to attack and eat.
[bright music]
Nature.
If I water them with
the watering pot
from the almighty farming tool,
they get bigger every day.
They're definitely growing
a lot faster than normal plants.
I'm still not exactly sure
what I'm growing,
but I hope it's stuff
that I can eat.
If they all turned out
to be decorative plants.
[Hiraku screams]
I'm sure that I'd fall
to my knees in despair.
[Hiraku sighs]
A few more days passed.
After all my hard work,
I was able to build a small hut.
I cut grooves into the wood
and stacked them
on top of each other.
It's basically a log house.
Part of the way through
I wasn't able to lift the lumber
up to the top anymore,
so I dug out the ground a bit
to give myself more room.
For the roof, I used
bark from the trees
and held it down with nails
I made from shaved down wood.
If I was in a fairy-tale,
a wolf would be able
to huff and puff
and blow this house down,
but I thought it was
a lot more civilized
than living in a tree hole.
I can't wait to see
how my crops turn out.
I feel really motivated lately,
and I've been looking
forward to each new day.
That was when I started
to get into a routine
with my new life here.
Dogs?
They're huge.
They don't seem like
they're going to attack me.
And they look like they're
in pretty rough shape.
[dog whimpers]
- [chuckles] Come on.
Perfect timing,
I just killed a boar
and didn't know what to do
with all the meat.
It was trying to get
over my fence
so I had no choice
but to exterminate it.
One of them has a swollen belly.
I wonder if he was trying to
take the pregnant one
somewhere safe when they were
attacked by some other animal.
This reminds me of when
I was a kid
and I wanted to get a dog.
They say that dogs are
a farmer's friend.
It'd be nice if they
hung around here.
[Dog whining]
What's wrong?
[dog growls]
Is she about to
give birth, here, now?
What should I do?
How can I help?
Well, it's probably better
than being outside
so I led them into my house.
How long does it take
for dogs to give birth?
Does she need water to drink?
It'll get colder
once the sun sets.
I should build a fire here.
But that'll fill
the room with smoke.
Maybe I can leave it
just outside the door.
[dog whimpering]
I tried doing everything
I could think of to help.
And I figured it wasn't good
for a human to be around,
so I left them alone.
I hope I didn't end up bothering
them by trying to help too much.
If that giant boar attacked
while she was giving birth
and unable to move,
[gentle suspenseful music]
It might be because of the light
from the fire next to the hut,
but everything else looks
really dark tonight.
[Hiraku sighs]
[Hiraku grunts]
Oh no, I fell asleep.
Uh, I'm coming in.
[puppies yapping]
[gentle cheerful music]
They look calm
now that it's all over,
but I'm sure she had
a really tough night.
Oh yeah.
To celebrate her giving birth,
I cut up the tastiest
looking parts from the boar.
I thought the dogs would go off
somewhere after she gave birth,
but it looks like they're
going to hang around here.
Since it seems like they're
really attached to that hut,
I can't bring myself
to kick them out.
So I built myself a new house.
I'd like to think I've improved
since the first home
that I built.
By the time the puppies
were old enough to start
running around,
the plants were big enough for
me to start harvesting them.
These are tomatoes.
Left alone, they grew
into a tangled mess.
They're pretty hard to harvest,
and they look kind of small.
But they're definitely tomatoes.
The dogs do some hunting and
protect the premises for me.
By the way, it's getting tricky
just calling them all dogs,
so I decided to give them names.
The boy is Kuro,
the girl is Yuki,
even though she's got dark fur.
Kuro, Yuki.
[upbeat music]
I didn't think dogs
would eat vegetables,
but seeing them enjoying
the vegetables so much
makes me want to work harder
to grow better ones
to feed them.
I've been pretty busy with
harvesting vegetables,
which makes me want to
shout with joy.
I'll need to build
a storehouse for them.
I want to build furniture
and tools, too.
There's a lot of stuff
I want to do.
[Hiraku sighs]
- [Hiraku] Well,
there's no rush.
I'll take my time working at it.
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
- You want to cross
the mountain?
Listen miss,
unless you're drunk,
you really shouldn't be
saying stuff like that.
Haven't you heard of
The Forest of Death?
That's what's you'll find on
the other side of the mountain.
It's full of dangerous monsters.
If any of them ever came
down here and attacked us,
we'd need guards on duty 24/7.
- Huh.
That might be just what I need.
[upbeat pastoral music]